We just finished
our acting class exam.
Next up, we're going to
get our bodies moving.
What we're playing today is
the Flag-Pulling Tournament.
Before the official match starts,
we'll first have a warm-up match
to get familiar with the feel and skills.
Here are the rules of the warm-up match.
First,
the eight students will draw lots to split into two teams.
Each round, the two teams
each send two students onto the field.
Each student wears two flags
in their team's color around their waist.
The two sides compete within the designated area.
The team that pulls off all
of the opponent's flags first wins the round.
You can start drawing lots now.
I got yellow.
Black. Yellow.
Here you come, Bro.
You drew one so fast.
Bro is here.
I'll take green.
Green, go over there.
Each team, discuss first
which two members will compete.
I want to give it a try,
because I'm just the courage guy,
not the brains.
So I'll be brave first
and see how it goes.
I want to try too.
Then you two go up.
You two go first.
Why do we go first?
Because compared to us two, you two look... taller.
No, his hand is injured.
I only have one hand left.
Your hand is injured?
Yeah.
I can grab like this,
Both are okay with me.
You two play rock-paper-scissors.
Whoever wins goes on with me.
Come on, rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, you're with me.
Three, two, one.
Start!
Come on, you've got this.
They picked the 1v1 mode.
If you can't beat them, run.
Come on!
Though you are younger,
I'm not going easy on you.
The two of us can move side by side like this.
No, listen to me. Pull apart first, like this.
Just like them.
Careful!
A sneak attack, he got...
Yeah, just like that.
It fell off.
Wait, you crossed the line.
Hold on.
Wait a second.
No.
It's fine.
Why did you get 'killed'?
Let's try again.
Come on, get him!
Mingyang, go!
Come on.
You got this, 1v2!
Congratulations to the Green team on winning.
Awesome!
Let's start the official match.
Director, do we have a trash-talk segment?
Sure.
Trash talk!
Go ahead.
You're all doomed!
You scared us to death.
You know why?
Because our momentum is unbeatable.
We're standing here right now.
We're like giants.
And you're like little dwarfs.
Alright.
Not much to say.
But we're standing
on your shoulders.
I don't even need to imagine beating you.
We're all the same age.
I didn't mean to crush you.
I think there's no need to say so much.
Just wait and see the results.
Okay.
Come on.
Now, the official game rules:
We'll continue with the two-team showdown format.
4V4, everyone plays.
Each team designates one member
as the captain
The first group to pull off
the opposing captain's two flags
wins.
I think it's like this.
They'll definitely choose
that guy as captain.
I recommend you, kid.
Yes.
I recommend you too.
Right.
Because they'll definitely think
we'll make you captain.
They'll come after you.
I think we're a bit too close.
Move back a bit.
They'll definitely think
I'll be the captain.
So don't make me captain.
You guys pick anyone as captain.
We'll predict their prediction.
We pretend he's the captain.
Right, pretend he's it.
I'm the captain.
I'll just keep hiding in the back.
Then you get them
to pick you as captain.
Right, just pick you as captain.
Right, you're less noticeable.
Right.
So we do this,
We'll do our triangle.
Then,
We walk around like this.
No, you stand at the very back.
I'll stand here.
You guys surround them like this.
Come on, hold hands.
You do it.
I'll go like this, I'll stand here.
The first round is about to start.
I think their captain might be Chen Zhixuan.
Three.
Two.
One.
Game start!
I can't get into the little corner.
Watch out!
This is intense.
How did a wristband fall off?
You two, pull apart.
Out!
Zhang Ziyu is eliminated.
Pull it off him!
He's definitely the captain.
Game over.
Congratulations to the Yellow team on winning.
Okay.
So who's your captain?
It's you?
I always thought it was him.
Alright, let's talk this over.
Let's huddle here and talk.
I feel like...
Actually, I think this time
it's really Sun Mingyang.
Who will you pick as captain next round?
Who will you pick?
Let's just say it directly. We pick him.
Yes, we pick him as captain.
Really?
Because they actually just said
you guys picked him.
He'll definitely make us think
it's not him.
But I think it's him.
I think it's him.
So how about this?
You be the captain, and I'll go distract him.
Sure.
So while we two are grabbing others,
Just try to keep him safe.
Then you be the main rusher.
Can you be the captain?
Sure.
You're captain again?
Yeah.
We just need to guess which one of them it is.
The tallest one is the captain.
Once we pull off the tallest one's flags, I think we'll win.
No matter who the captain is,
we pull anyway.
Pull it!
If you suck, practice more.
No way.
I already pulled off your flags.
I've lost both of mine.
Right?
Game over.
Congratulations to the Yellow team on winning.
That was amazing.
Come on.
We figured you out.
What? What?
Too bad.
Do we play three rounds, sir?
Congratulations.
We'll give you our
Deluxe Toiletry Bag.
Where is it?
You'll share your Deluxe Toiletry Bag in your dorm later.
Okay.
Back to the dorm.
Since this is communal living
and dorm space is limited,
the show has decided to streamline everyone's luggage.
Next up is a
Luggage Lightening Challenge.
Students will have twenty seconds
to rescue the items they want to bring into the dorm.
You can wear them, hang them, or whatever.
As long as it stays on your body and doesn't touch the ground,
it counts as successfully carried.
Twenty seconds.
Hanging on our bodies.
Does wearing it count?
Yes.
Anything in your mouth counts too.
Is there anything that we absolutely need to survive?
What do we do?
It's basically all clothes.
So personal items have to be worn on the body.
What about personal items then?
Since Bai Guanyu
got first place in the first Placement Assessment,
as a reward, he'll get double the time,
which is forty seconds.
Well, thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, then I'll go first.
I'll go first.
I'm a little nervous.
He brought a gaming laptop.
Yes, this one's a must.
Five.
Four.
Three.
That fast?
Two.
One.
Time's up.
Alright, that's it then.
This is all I have.
This is my big bag of snacks.
What do I do with this?
Just deal with it.
The time was so short.
Even your double time wasn't really enough.
I'm totally lost.
We'll hold onto it for now.
Okay.
Open this pocket first.
Right.
Their pants don't have pockets.
And unlock the code?
Chen Zhixuan, fifteen seconds have already passed.
He keeps dropping items, Bro.
And these are all
some supplements I brought.
You can all drink these.
Things you can mix with water.
And I also randomly grabbed some clothes
and my comfort objects.
Come on, let's lay it flat first.
Hurry, let's lay it flat first.
Three, two, one, go!
This one needs a code.
Another combination lock.
Oh no.
Isn't this taking too long?
It's okay.
He's got double the time.
Time is running out for Bai Guanyu.
Fifteen seconds left.
He's searching, rummaging around.
What's he looking for?
He opened the box on the other side.
And he's giving commentary too.
It won't open. It's stuck.
He pulled out a Pochacco.
He searched forever and pulled out a pillow.
So these are everyone's comfort objects?
Every generation has its own comfort objects.
Each one has a comfort object.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Time's up!
Come on, introduce it to everyone.
First of all,
Everyone has a comfort objects.
Right, it's something you have to
hold while you sleep every day.
A foot-soaking bucket.
Also a daily essential.
And then,
The gifts I brought for everyone inside
are actually pretty practical.
Mystery snacks.
If there's a chance tonight,
I can share them with everyone.
You can look forward to it.
Mystery snacks.
I'm not eating bugs.
My hobby is wellness.
I love all kinds of insects.
It's a secret.
And this is for everyone.
I prepared a pack for each person.
It's a wellness tea I blended myself.
And then,
it's for 'replenishing blood'.
I think we hot-blooded young people
need that.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Pajamas.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Stop.
Then you're at a big disadvantage without a bag.
I picked a random pile of clothes.
This is my skincare bag.
And this is the comfort object that I need to hug when sleeping.
Then my toiletry bag and earphones.
Done.
I'll move all this stuff into here, okay?
That one's not there.
No face towel there.
There are face towels.
There are.
Really, I just saw them.
Then remember to bring face towels.
Each of us takes one.
And take one that we need.
Then each of us takes.
Right, we must.
Right.
I'll just take face masks.
I'll just take the face towel.
Nothing else at all.
Fighting for the face towel.
Put it here.
This spot needs a face towel ad placement.
Anything in your mouth counts too.
Three.
Two.
One.
My contact lenses.
My towel.
These are spare underwear and socks.
Disposable underwear and socks. And this is my guitar.
You actually kept your guitar?
This is my...
I can't live without this.
It's for nighttime.
It's just like comfort objects.
You have to hold it when you sleep?
Holding it, falling asleep while playing guitar.
Playing guitar.
The lullaby is up to you two then.
Lullaby.
Your turn.
My turn.
Do I still need to zip it up?
I'm so nervous.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Stop.
Feet apart.
Knees apart.
Quite something.
It keeps leaking.
What's this?
These are my pants, my clothes.
And that's all.
So embarrassing.
He's already raring to go, Jiang Xiaomeng.
All ready.
Even warming up.
Go!
This is so convenient.
So minimal.
My underwear.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Okay.
Next time I'll just dump everything into one plastic bag.
Right.
This is the big toiletry bag I brought.
And this is for reducing puffiness.
Also my
underwear.
Sir, if I may point something out,
it seems none of us brought face towels, right?
It seems so...
Remember to bring face towels.
I'll just bring face towels.
Nothing else at all.
Fighting for face towels.
Put it here.
If you don't mind, use this to wipe.
Is that underwear?
I can cut these pants open.
For you to wipe with.
So touching.
We have one more guest, okay?
Let's not rush.
Get ready.
This kind of box is better.
This one's too hard to carry.
Face towels.
You can take other stuff.
Five.
Four.
That scared me.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Face towels.
So grateful.
Please accept my bow, bro.
I brought lots of face towels,
and also makeup remover,
eye drops,
glasses,
facial cleanser.
Got everything.
Not bad.
It's all stuff I don't have.
It's all stuff we don't have.
Why did nobody take mine away?
Don't even mention it.
No idea what it is.
Got nothing.
Nothing happened.
I don't know.
Next,
all students,
please take your belongings to the dorms.
So cozy.
It's big.
What's this?
Who's this?
Hello.
So should we choose our beds first?
Yeah.
Right, let's allocate the beds.
Allocate the beds.
Or we could just draw lots.
Drawing lots.
That works too.
Drawing lots works.
Draw lots.
Let's say the one closest to the door is number one.
One, two, three, four.
Then over here.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Does that work?
Yes.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Then I'll take this one.
Hurry up and take it.
Hello everyone.
We just finished
the dorm room draw.
And the one I drew is...
Bed number four.
Bed number two.
This is fate.
I'm bed number three.
Bed three.
I'm bed number six.
I'm number five.
Six, seven, eight, here they come.
Honestly, I didn't want to get the outer side.
In here.
Same here.
Right.
The inside feels safer.
This little corner, I swear
makes me feel so safe.
With my bag packed, bed number two.
I'm just over here,
like a whole...
I'm all dirty.
I'm dead tired.
Me too.
Sleepy.
For the first time, by nine o'clock I was already dying to sleep.
Seriously.
Welcome to the Incomplete Summer Training Camp.
Hello, teachers.
Our class has already begun.
What?
Who did it?
The preparation time is two hours.
You weren't immersed in your own character.
I think that loses you a few points.
The endings are never clear.
But you haven't fully brought out those three layers.
I think the structure of this piece might need some more thought.